Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series C. 1947 CONVENTION RESOLUTIONS
  - Sub-Series 500-141. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 141
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1948-1952 (Box 614, Folder 46)
      February 1948-52.
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 47)
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947-1948 (Box 614, Folder 48)
      December 20, 1947-January 1948.
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 49)
      November 28, 1947-December 19, 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 50)
      October 22, 1947-November 27, 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 51)
      September 3, 1947-October 21, 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Section, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 52)
      May-August 1947.
    - Pennsylvania Section. Auxiliary Lodges by Board of Adjustment for use in connection with Convention Resolution No. 141, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 500-142. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 142
    - Grant Local Lodges right to deny admission to visiting members, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 500-143. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 143
    - Endorse and support program for immediate entry of displaced Europeans, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 500-144. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 144
    - Authorize Grand President to establish and assist in support of Legislative Committees in sparsely populated states, 1947-1956 (Box 614, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 500-145. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 145
    - Condemning State anti-labor legislation and commending State Legislative Boards, 1947 (Box 614, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 500-146. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 146
    - To oppose H.R. 2657, "Administrative Practitioners Act", 1947 (Box 614, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 500-147. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 147
    - To support H.R. 2007 and S.J.R. 67, establishing Commission for Study of Legal Status of Women, 1947-1951 (Box 614, Folder 59)
    - To support H.R. 2007 and S.J.R. 67, establishing Commission for Study of Legal Status of Women. Transcript of Hearings Before House Judiciary Committee on Equal Rights Amendment to Constitution and Commission on Legal Status of Women, 1948 (Box 614, Folder 60)
      March 10-12, 1948.
  - Sub-Series 500-148. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 148
    - Establish minimum hourly wage of 65 cents per hour, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 500-149. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 149
    - Endorse Wagner-Ellender-Taft Housing Bill, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 500-150. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 150
    - To oppose H.R. 1639, amending Federal Employees' Liability Act, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 500-151. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 151
    - Endorse H.R. 2408, Increasing Parcel Post Rates, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 500-152. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 152
    - Protesting enactment of restrictive labor laws, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 500-153. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 153
    - Endorse current wage increase movement, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 500-154. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 154
    - To establish uniform wage scales, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 500-155. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 155
    - Oppose Communist, Fascist and Nazi organizations., 1947-1951 (Box 615, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 500-156. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 156
    - To extend scope rules to cover entire craft or class, 1947-1950 (Box 615, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 500-157. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 157
    - To expedite handling of grievances, 1947-1950 (Box 615, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 500-158. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 158
    - No discrimination against women, 1947-1951 (Box 615, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 500-159. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 159
    - To provide greater safety and safeguard health of Express employees, 1947-1949 (Box 615, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 500-160. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 160
    - To protect health and safety of employees, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 500-161. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 161
    - To eliminate short-hour work, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 500-162. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 162
    - Punitive rates for overtime, Sunday and holiday work, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 500-163. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 163
    - Better cooperation and coordination of efforts of Lodges and System Boards, 1947-1951 (Box 615, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 500-164. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 164
    - Consolidations, coordinations, abandonments or dissolution of existing facilities, 1947-1955 (Box 615, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 500-165. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 165
    - Organizing activities of System Boards and Local Lodges, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 500-166. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 166
    - To organize highway motor transport and bus terminals, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 500-167. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 167
    - To organize air transport industry, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 500-168. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 168
    - Our organizing campaign, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 500-169. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 169
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 500-170. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 170
    - Consolidation of Transportation Agencies, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 500-171. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 171
    - Increase vacations after 15 years' service, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 500-172. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 172
    - To suspend informers, spotters, etc., 1947 (Box 615, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 500-173. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 173
    - To cooperate in reducing loss or damage claims, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 500-174. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 174
    - To equalize rates of pay, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 500-175. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 175
    - Time and one-half pay for vacation not allowed when scheduled, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 500-176. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 176
    - To publish National Railroad Adjustment Board Awards in Bulletin, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 500-177. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 177
    - To equalize rates of pay, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 500-178. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 178
    - To standardize wages, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 500-179. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 179
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 500-180. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 180
    - To issue referendum ballot on Crosser Act, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 500-181. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 181
    - Transportation privileges for Express employees, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 500-182. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 182
    - Transportation for Express Messengers, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 500-183. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 183
    - Amend Vacation Agreement, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 500-184. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 184
    - Pay for holidays, double-time when worked, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 500-185. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 185
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 500-186. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 186
    - To amend Railroad Retirement and Unemployment Insurance Acts, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 500-187. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 187
    - Guaranteed Annual Wage, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 500-188. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 188
    - Condemning Railway Express Agency attitude toward Blue Cross, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 500-189. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 189
    - Increase annuities under Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 500-190. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 190
    - To elect System Board Officers by referendum vote, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 500-191. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 191
    - Require approval of 51% of members to divide Lodge and Issue new Charter, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 500-192. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 192
    - To amend system of reporting per capita tax to Grand Lodge and System Boards, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 500-193. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 193
    - To elect System Board Officers by referendum vote, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 500-194. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 194
    - To increase Brotherhood death benefit, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 500-195. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 195
    - Protesting delay in handling grievances by National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 500-196. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 196
    - To establish Welfare Fund for transportation workers, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 500-197. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 197
    - Protesting treatment accorded veterans of World War II, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 500-198. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 198
    - To amend Vacation Agreement, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 500-199. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 199
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 500-200. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 200
    - To amalgamate railroad workers in United States and Canada, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 500-201. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 201
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 500-202. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 202
    - 40-hour week, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 500-203. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 203
    - Condemning Crosser Amendments, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 500-204. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 204
    - Liberalize free transportation privilege, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 500-205. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 205
    - 40-hour work week, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 500-206. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 206
    - Revise Vacation Agreement, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 500-207. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 207
    - Request for sick leave rule, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 500-208. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 208
    - Pay for holidays, double-time when worked, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 500-209. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 209
    - Remove restrictions on free transportation, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 500-210. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 210
    - Preserve equitable wage differential, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 500-211. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 211
    - Permit Local Chairmen in Joint Lodge to represent employees of more than one carrier, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 500-212. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 212
    - Messengers to accompany all Express cars worked en route, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 500-213. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 213
    - All Express to be handled by Express employees, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 500-214. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 214
    - Commending Congressman Crosser, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 500-215. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 215
    - Amend Death Benefit, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 500-216. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 216
    - Post-war program, 1947-1948 (Box 615, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 500-217. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 217
    - Protesting reactionary legislation, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 500-218. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 218
    - Commending opening address and program of Grand President, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 500-219. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 219
    - Demand vacation credit for armed forces, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 500-220. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 220
    - Amend Railroad Retirement Act, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 500-221. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 221
    - Restore continuity of membership to furloughed members who were given withdrawal cards in Depression years, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 500-222. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 222
    - To establish retirement insurance system for full-time officers and employees of Grand Lodge and System Boards, 1947-1955 (Box 615, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 500-223. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 223
    - To conduct newspaper and radio campaign against anti-labor legislation, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 500-224. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 224
    - Expressing appreciation to Pullman Company and Canadian Pacific and Canadian National Railways, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 500-225. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 225
    - Thanking Railway Companies, Hotels and other organizations for courtesies extended, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 500-226. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 226
    - Extending appreciation to citizens, city officials, Local Committee on Arrangements and Committee in Charge of Entertainment, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 79)
  - Sub-Series 500-227. 1947 Convention Resolutions. Resolution No. 227
    - Labor unity, 1947 (Box 615, Folder 80)